我卵蛋都要冻掉了
Freezing my balls off.
没那么糟 放松
It ain't so bad. Loosen up.
再几个月就春天了
Couple more months, it's gonna be spring.
春天 哈?
Spring, huh?
听着
Listen,
你要搞清楚上面把你派来是放你条生路
you gotta realize the bosses did you a favor sending you down here.
- 市局呼叫水警队 - 7672回话 请说
- Citywide to Marine Unit. - 7672. Go ahead.
私人船只呼救
Distress call from a private craft.
60尺白色船只 引擎熄火
60-foot white vessel. Engines are dead.
事发地点 市局?
What's the location, Citywide?
桥边河道
In the channel near the bridge.
距Armistead码头约2000码处
About 2,000 yards off the Armistead pier.
明白 即刻前往
10-4, we're responding.
巴尔的摩市是美重要的海港之一 专设水警编制
我老爸以前在那做事
My father used to work there.
- Beth钢厂? - 对 就是造船厂那儿
- Beth Steel? - In the shipyards there, yeah.
我叔叔以前在那儿做监管员
I had an uncle who was a supervisor there.
不过78年就失业了
Got laid off in '78, though.
我爸是73年
'73 for my dad.
- 派对船? - 嗯 还不错
- Party boat? - Pretty one, yeah.
应该不止一个引擎不是吗
More than one engine, right?
也许是电器故障
Probably an electrical problem.
那是水警船?
Is that a police boat?
- 你今晚怎样 - 很高兴见到你
How are you tonight? Good to see you.
Henry 最近可好
Henry, how are you?
- 来一杯? - 不 谢谢
- Drink? - No, thanks.
- 你是船长? - 对
- You're the Captain? - Yeah.
- 港务局的? - 不 市警
- Harbormaster? - No, City Police.
你们发动不了了?
So you're dead in the water?
我想是启动装置的问题
Think it's the starter.
- 你不是技师吧 - 我? 不是
- You're not a mechanic, are you? - Me? No.
我连船头船尾都分不清
I can't tell the aft from the stern.
我顶多能帮你拖个船
Best I can offer you is a tow line.
Claude 看来我们得用拖的了
Claude, looks like they're gonna need a pull.
- 明白 我们把它拖到Henderson码头 - 可以
- 10-4, we'll tow to Henderson's. - That'll work.
你能不能晚点再带我们回去
Any chance you can hold off on bringing us in?
派对正开着呢
Lot of partying going on now.
我不想因为一点引擎问题就败兴而归
I wouldn't wanna cut it short for a little engine trouble.
你们拦在河道上
You're in the shipping channel.
你可以把我们拖离河道
You tow us somewhere out of the way,
让乐队多奏一段
and the band plays on a while longer.
火线重案组 第二季 第一集 风生水起
The Wire S02E01 Ebb Tide
《Way Down in the Hole》 第二季演唱:汤姆·威茨（Tom Waits）
* When you walk through the garden *
* You gotta watch your back *
* Well I beg your pardon *
* Walk the straight and narrow track *
* If you walk with Jesus *
* He's gonna save your soul *
* You gotta keep the devil *
* Way down in the hole *
* He's got the fire and the fury *
* At his command *
* Well you don't have to worry *
* If you hold on to Jesus hand *
* We'll all be safe from Satan *
* When the thunder rolls *
* Just gotta help me keep the devil *
* Way down in the hole *
* You gotta help me keep the devil *
"不复当年咯"  ---Little Big Roy
...因为你知道我在说什么 对吧
...because you see what I'm saying, right?
我是说 我缉拿赃车三年却一无所获
I mean, three years in auto theft and I didn't learn anything.
我没兴趣
I didn't care.
我告诉你 当时我甚至不想干警察了
I'm telling you, I didn't even wanna be a police anymore.
我说真的
I honestly didn't.
我想就为这个我才开枪打我的车
I think that was why I shot up my car like I did.
但我们在Barksdale案中做的工作
But this thing we did on Barksdale,
窃听还有其他那些...
the wiretap and all...
那些才有意义
that felt like something.
那些才是我想干的
That felt like something I wanna do.
所以我想
So I was thinking,
你知道 也许我能去缉毒科
you know, narcotics, maybe.
警长 这东西放哪
Major, you want this stuff where?
就这儿 那边靠墙放
Just in here. Up against the wall over there.
如果缉毒科那边没空缺...
If there aren't any openings in the regular narcotics shift...
查抄科也成
maybe assets forfeiture or something like that.
轻点 东西要摔坏了
Easy. Everything breaks.
我是说 在Barksdale案中...
I mean, with this Barksdale thing...
Lester Freamon领着我们查资金
Lester Freamon had us deep into the money.
查得很深
Real deep.
我们本可以查抄房产
We could've seized real estate,
现金 车辆还有其他的东西
cash, vehicles, all kinds of stuff.
如果上面 我是说 如果指挥部让我们查下去
If the bosses, I mean, if command had let that case go forward.
立马就能行动
We were on it.
看这个 和平鸽
Look at that. It's the dove.
是啊
Right.
- 那你怎么想 - 我怎么想
- So what do you think? - What do I think?
我想...
I think--
你下月参加警司考试
you're gonna take the Sergeant's Exam next month.
因为我能跟Andy Krawczyk通通气...
And because I have Andy Krawczyk's ear...
而他能跟市政厅通气...
and because he has City Hall's ear...
你的警司做定了
you're gonna make Sergeant.
接着你过来东南区...
Then you're gonna come out here to the Southeast...
在这儿 有你岳父我...
where, because I'm your father-in-law...
你就能到一个太平的部门
you're gonna be assigned a daytime shift
干日班
in a quiet sector.
接着你再参加警督考试
Then you're gonna take the Lieutenant's Exam
同样会拿高分
where you'll also score high.
我对警衔没兴趣
I don't want to make rank.
我想查案 大案
I want to work cases. Good cases.
Roland
Roland.
听我说
Listen to me.
毒品案中你表现不错
You did good with the drug thing.
你全力以赴完成了分内事
You buckled down, you did the work.
除了大陪审团那破事...
And except for that thing with the Grand Jury...
你给自己洗清了不少名誉
you helped take some of the stink off yourself.
如果你现在能闭上嘴好好听我说...
Now if you'll just shut up and listen to me...
你在局里才可能仕途顺畅
you might actually have a career in this department.
这收音机不怎么好使
This radio ain't working that well.
是我们快收不到了
We're losing it.
是我们快收不到电台了
We're losing the station, man.
什么意思
What you mean?
我们离Baltimore很远了 就要收不到那电台了
We done gone so far from Baltimore, we're losing the station.
试试费城的电台吧
Try a Philly station or some shit like that.
它在费城的频率不一样?
The radio in Philly is different?
小子 你搞笑吧你?
Nigger, you gotta be fucking with me, right?
你就没听过Baltimore之外的电台?
You never heard a station outside of Baltimore?
除了进少管所那次 我从没离开Baltimore
I ain't never left Baltimore except that Boys' Village shit one day.
在那烂地方我也不会想听广播
And I wasn't trying to hear no radio up in that bitch.
拜托 伙计 难听死了 别转了
Come on, man. You're killing me. Stop.
"今天是个种番茄的好天气"
It's been perfect tomato weather out there.
"又湿又热"
These wonderful hot, humid days,
"晚上还会下雨"
and then rain at night.
- 这是费城的电台? - 我他妈怎么知道
- This a Philly station? - How the fuck would I know?
怎么大家都想离开Baltimore呢 实在想不通
Why would anybody wanna leave Baltimore? That's what I'm asking.
- 嘿 出口到了 - 走那边
Yo, that be the exit. Take that shit.
目前为止还挺上道
So far they on it.
喂 老朋友
Ahoy, matey.
女孩们常说什么船上的小子
The girls always tell me about the little man in the boat.
现在我算明白她们在说什么了
Now I know who they talking about.
上来伙计
Come on board, man.
- 上来 让你看看 - 靠 不上
- Come on, I wanna show you. - Fuck, no.
- 怎么了 - Bunk我不会游泳
- What's the matter? - The Bunk can't swim.
也不太擅长浮在水上
I ain't too good at floating, either.
那什么风把你吹到水边来了
So what brings you to the water's edge?
Ilene Nathan给我打电话
Ilene Nathan called.
Gant的案子还有四周开庭
Gant case is coming up in four weeks.
她要给证人做些准备工作
She wants to start doing preliminaries on our witnesses.
也就是说 公房区的老太问题不大
That means the old lady from the projects, which is no problem.
而你的人Omar不知所踪
And your man Omar, who's in the wind.
你有Omar的消息吧 Jimmy?
You got a line on Omar, Jimmy?
哦 他不在右舷
Well, he's not to starboard.
那叫左舷 傻帽
That's port, fool.
你他妈怎么知道
How the fuck would you know?
拜托
Come on.
午餐我请 然后我们一起想想怎么办
Let me buy you lunch and we can think on this shit together.
要走得先跟我队长说一声
I leave, I gotta tell my Sergeant.
这倒提醒了我
That reminds me.
Landsman要讨回他的10美元
Landsman wants his $10.
什么理由
What for?
他打赌你会来开船
For betting that you'd ride the boat.
你告诉那混球少做梦...
You tell that motherfucker he's not gonna see that money...
尤其很可能就是他 告诉Rawls我不想去哪
especially since it was probably him told Rawls where I didn't wanna go.
噢 Jimmy 那边少了你就不一样了
Ain't the same up there without your ass.
- 哦 不一样? - 事实上 好多了
- No? - Better, actually.
嘿 别乱来
Hey, come on, now.
疏通运河... 就意味着我们齐活了
The canal gets dredged... it means we all work.
你的人 我的人
Your people, my people.
运河是关键 Nat 你很清楚
The canal's the key, Nat. You know this.
是啊 但你知道花多少钱...
Yeah, but you know how much money you're gonna spend...
才能让他们讨论一下这屁事吗
to even get them talking about that shit?
不搏一把 我们就坐以待毙吧
We don't take a shot, we might as well roll over and die right now.
不 你让他们重建粮食码头
No, you get them to rebuild the grain pier.
- 那已经有了百艘的吞吐量 - 那是卸货的 Nat
- You got a 100 ships right there. - That's break-bulk, Nat.
最火时也就是一周多一两班
Best you'll do is one or two extra gangs a week on them blowers.
一班顶多六到七人
That's six or seven-man gangs at best.
是啊 但那么做总有些甜头
yeah, But you try for that, you might actually come away with something.
如果你去Annapolis要求 开那该死的运河...
You go down to Annapolis asking for the goddamn canal...
你就等着一无所获 拿着自己干瘪的老二回来吧
you gonna come back with nothing but your little shriveled-ass dick in your hand.
更何况
What's more,
如果不尽快建好粮食码头...
if the grain pier don't get fixed up soon...
那些混蛋会把那儿建满共管公寓的(各单位产权独立的高级公寓)
some asshole's gonna fuck us by building condominiums all over it.
Nat 如果运河能有两尺深...
Nat, if the canal were 2 feet deeper--
去他的运河
Fuck the canal.
我要去区议会
I'm going to the District Council.
让他们推动重建粮食码头
I'm gonna tell them to push for the grain pier.
- 理解了吗 - Nat 他妈的冷静点
- You feel me? - Nat, calm the fuck down.
你们这些该死的工会委员
Goddamn Checkers Local always acting
成天摆出一副国王样
like you're the king of everything and shit.
Nat 听我说 如果我们...
Nat, listen to me. If we--
你们就该爬回船舱里...
Y'all need to crawl back down in them holds...
想清楚自己叫什么 打哪来的
and remind yourself of who you is and where you come from.
该死 Frank
Damn, Frank.
我们刚刚就坐着 看Nat Coxson
We just sat here and watched Nat Coxson
把你骂得狗血淋头
take a shit all over you.
说你这混球老二干瘪 你还就认了
And shrivel-dick motherfucker that you are, you take it.
想知道就告诉你 我每天早上醒来
For your information... I wake up every morning
都是一柱擎天
with an angry, blue-veined diamond-cutter.
我本来要向47区的会长展示一下...
I was gonna enlighten the president of Local 47 on this particular point...
但他就这么走了
and he chose to depart.
一柱擎天 各位
Blue steel, gentlemen.
看在上帝的份上
For Christ's sake.
三寸半硬钢
Three-and-a-half inches of hard blue steel.
Nicky小子 你今天接到活了?
Nicky boy, you working today?
当Big Roy组的监工
As a lasher for Big Roy's crew.
好啊 光宗耀祖啊
Attaboy. Make the family proud.
两周来首次开工
First day they give me in two weeks.
- Ott在吗 - 老地方
- Is Ott around? - On his ass as usual.
那混蛋还欠我20块买乐透的钱
Worthless fuck still owes me $20 for them lotto tickets.
嘿 Nick
Hey, Nick.
你去见"希腊人"取号码
You need to see the Greek and get a number.
- 他有货要过来 - 今天?
- He's got one on the way. - Today?
明天
Tomorrow.
Atlantic Light号 在北角
The Atlantic Light over at North Point.
好的
All right.
嘿 Frank
Yo, Frank.
什么事
What's up?
你得跟Ziggy谈谈 伙计 他搞得一团糟
You gotta get with Ziggy, man. He's all over the place.
我八点就在这儿了
I'm here since 8:00.
你很清楚我八点就在这儿了
You know I been here since 8:00.
- 沉住气 - 你个呆头鹅
- Hold your horses. - You fucking goose.
我会找给你的 你消停一下行不
I'm gonna find it for you. Just shut the fuck up a minute.
怎么回事
How we doing?
- 没什么问题 长官 - 去你的没问题
- Ain't a problem, Chief. - The fuck it ain't.
我八点就到这儿等着装货了...
I'm down here since 8:00 for crane-to-chassis...
而这"崔弟鸟"(华纳动画里的卡通鸟)把我的集装箱弄丢了
and Tweety Bird here lost the can.
丢不了
It ain't lost.
载货单上写的明明白白 哪去了 Zig?
It's right here on the manifest as a hot box. Where is it, Zig?
要么在7区...
It's either in Bay 7, or--
7区是空的 伙计
Bay 7 is empty, man.
要么不在 如果是那样...
Or it ain't. In that case...
肯定在这堆里面
it's definitely somewhere in the stacks.
耶稣他妈的基督
Jesus fucking Christ.
你要把我逼疯了 Ziggy 你他妈要把我逼疯了
You're killing me here, Ziggy. You are fucking killing me.
给我你代理商的电话 我会跟他们结清的
Get me a number for your shipping agent. I'll call and try to square it.
还有你
And you.
现在收工 别管那集装箱了 别再滚回来了
You clock out today and leave your box, and don't ever come the fuck back.
听清楚了吗 Zig?你被炒了
You hear me, Zig? You're fired.
迟些再找你算账 蠢货
Later for you, goofus.
操蛋的家伙
Fucking guy.
工作都丢了还满不在乎
He loses his job and he couldn't care less.
- 他不会被炒的 伙计 - 不会?
- He ain't fired, man. - No?
那是他老爸
That's his father.
你要得多急
How fast you need this?
案子一个月后开庭 这周就要开始准备
Case goes to trial in a month. Got to start prepping it this week.
Burns警官
Officer Burns.
警探
Detective.
听说他们把你踢到这下面
I heard they posted you down here.
但 我想说 你知道 该死
But, I mean, you know, damn.
那些混球来真的 不是吗
These motherfuckers don't play, do they?
你下来做什么
So what brings you downstairs?
我来取Gant案的证物
I was pulling evidence on the Gant case.
你知道 Bird的庭审
You know, trial date for Bird
下个月开庭 Ilene Nathan想做好准备
is next month and llene Nathan wanted to be ready.
带我向他问好
You give him my love.
- 谁 - Bird
- Who? - Bird.
没有证物
No evidence.
你什么意思 没有证物?
What do you mean, no evidence?
提交书上写的是"BB排 14区 3架..."
Submission slip says "Row BB, Section 14, Shelf 3...
"4号 右后方" 就这样
"Four, Right rear." It says that.
然后呢
So?
没这东西 BB只有12区 这上面写14
No such thing. BB has 12 sections. This says 14.
明白我说的了吗?
You see what I'm saying?
没有证据
No evidence.
"冬天冻死了大部分弱小的毛虫品种"
Winters kill off the weaker varieties of caterpillars.
- 开玩笑 - "...那是个完全不同的品种...."
- Fuck me. - ...that's of an entirely different breed....
靠
Fuck.
道路封锁
"...为抵御毛虫 他们整个冬天都在进食"
...protection against caterpillars, they eat right through it.
"但这只是一种警示系统"
But it is a sort of a warning system.
他们到了
They here.
Franoosh 你来了
Franoosh, you made it.
是的 神父 我帮你搞定了
Right, Father. Got you covered here.
过来
Come on.
想看看你的窗吗
You wanna see your window?
只有Franoosh Sobotka
Only Franoosh Sobotka would
尽一切办法从Esslingen找来彩色玻璃
send all the way to Esslingen for stained glass.
德国人顽固
The Germans are hard-headed,
但手艺无人能比
but you can't beat them for craft.
神父 我很高兴能为教堂做这些  你知道
I was glad to do it, Father, for the church, you know.
事实上我有事请你帮忙作为回报
Truth is I need to ask you something in return.
愿尽全力
Anything I can do.
我想跟参议员面谈
I need some face time with the Senator.
Barbara?
她周日来做早弥撒 波兰语的
She comes to the early mass on Sunday, the one in Polish.
我们现在麻烦不断 神父
We got nothing but problems, Father.
得让C&D运河(Chesapeake & Delaware运河)有点动静...
We need to see something happen with the C&D Canal...
粮食码头也已经停工一年了
and the grain pier's been down for a year.
我听过不少硬汉忏悔一些闻所未闻的事
I got tough guys coming in to confess things I never heard before.
你不必告诉我现在码头的情况有多糟
I don't need you to tell me how bad things are at the docks.
那你会尽快安排好和Mikulski见面?
So you'll set something up with Mikulski soon?
请我帮忙用不着捐德国窗玻璃 Francis
You didn't need a German window to ask me for that, Francis.
更何况...
And what's more...
你所给予的
you've made offerings way above
已经远远超过了这扇窗户的代价
what it would take to get that window up there.
你有多久没忏悔了
How long since your last confession?
回见 神父
I'll see you, Father.
东西大概在别的地方 伙计
This shit might be somewhere else, man.
东西往常都在门里 伙计
Yo, the shit is always up in the door, man.
混球 你一直在旁边盯着
Motherfucker, you been standing there watching us.
有看见我们找到什么吗
You see any shit come up out of there?
你也看见了 车里什么也没有
You seen we ain't take shit up off this car.
- 好了 - 你也看见了
- All right. - You seen it.
谁会相信 东西丢了
Who gonna believe us? This shit is missing.
你少说废话
And fuck what you're saying.
就告诉他那东西他妈的丢了
All he's gonna hear is that this shit is fucking missing.
嘿 再找一遍
Yo, check it again.
东西不在这 打电话告诉你的人
Yo, the shit ain't there, man. Call your man and say so.
小子 你说什么
Nigger, what you say?
- 我说了再找一遍 该死 - 哇哦 冷静点
- I said check it again, God damn it! - Whoa, chill.
嘿 伙计 别再吵了
Yo, man, cut that shit the fuck out.
今天它妈的怎么回事 伙计?
What the fuck is going on today, man?
他们还真磨洋工 不是吗
Taking their time, ain't they?
该死 怎么回事
What the hell is going on?
搞什么
Come on, man.
该死
Damn!
也不在这区
Ain't anywhere in this section either.
看看下一排
Start on the next row.
队长 那俩袋子可能在 这地下室的任何地方
Lieutenant, those two bags could be anywhere in this damn basement.
没错
You're right.
- 我们整晚都要耗这儿了 - 没错
- We could be here all night. - Right again.
那就是加班咯?
So that's overtime, right?
靠 我还是打不好字
Fuck me. I still cannot type.
混蛋白人小鬼 我喜欢他们
Fucking white boys, I love them.
- 我爱死他们了 - 哦?
- I fucking love them. - Yeah?
蠢得什么似地
Dumb as a box of rocks.
- 谁? - 白人小鬼
- Who? - White boys.
我是说我查的Kane街上的那些脑残
Talking about the brain-deads in my Kane Street case.
我叫他过来 跟他说要买些毒品
I call him up, I tell him I wanna buy some drugs.
你猜他说什么
You know what he says?
"好 我卖给你 你要多少"
"Okay, I'll sell you the drugs. How much drugs do you want?"
我对天发誓 Kima 他们不说暗语
I swear to God, Kima, they don't code it,
不要另行会面 啥都没有
they don't ask for a meet, nothing.
等交易谈妥了  也没有跑腿的 屁都没一个
And then when you make the deal, there's no runner, no bullshit.
那家伙自己就过来对你说
It's the guy himself walking up to you, saying:
"毒品我带来了 你钱带了没有"
"I brought the drugs. Did you bring the money?"
我不是开玩笑 查了那些白痴两周后...
I'm not kidding. I have much respect for black people...
我对黑人兄弟充满了敬仰
after working with these idiots for two weeks.
如果白人小鬼想在Baltimore贩毒
If white boys wanna sell drugs in Baltimore,
他们得重新制定一套法律...
they have to make different laws for it...
好对他们"公平"点
Iike even it out for them.
平权措施：司法中为消除歧视 保护弱势群体利益的措施
"平权措施"
Affirmative action.
不让一个白人掉队
Leave no white man behind.
Herc 你究竟干什么来了
What the fuck do you want?
让你没收些东西
I need you to do the seizures.
有产权证 契约或登记吗 你有哪一样?
You got titles, deeds, registrations? What do you have for me?
你不就干这个的吗 你是在财产罚没科 不是吗
Thought you did that. You're the Forfeiture Unit, right?
我为市律师撰写陈述书和档案
I write all the affidavits and the filing for the City Solicitor.
但你得给我要查抄的东西的文件
But you've gotta give me the information on what we're taking.
那太麻烦了
That's a fucking hassle.
想要没收 把文书填好
You want the property, do the paperwork.
你该长进了 Herc
You gotta step up, Herc.
现在没有我和Carver帮你
You don't have me or Carver to lean on here.
不行?
No?
那你明天来参加搜查怎么样?
How about you come on the raids tomorrow?
看在过去的份上 跟我一起敲几扇门
Take a few doors with me for old time's sake.
你要入室搜查?
You taking doors?
嗯 Kane街的两间房和一家酒吧
Yeah, two houses and a bar on Kane Street.
来吧 Kima 跟我们一起吧 我知道你怀念那种生活
Come on, Kima, mount up with us. I know you miss it.
我不用在贫民区打滚了
I'm done rolling around the gutter.
现在我坐办公室
I am inside now.
你现在宅起来了?
You're a housecat now?
我答应过人家
I made a promise.
我得说 Kima 如果你是男的...
I gotta say, Kima. If you were a guy...
事实上 从某些方面说 你比我认识的多数男人都要厉害
and, actually, in some ways you're better than most guys I know.
如果你是男的 你的朋友 会给你买杯啤酒然后跟你说
If you were a guy, your friends would buy you a beer and let you know.
跟我说什么
Let me know what?
- 你真他妈惧内 - 惧内?
- You're fucking whipped. - Whipped?
被老婆整得服服帖帖的
Pussy-whipped within an inch of your life.
没开玩笑
I kid you not.
那...
So...
那?
So?
那我们到哪找Omar
So where do we find Omar?
谁
Who?
他还说什么了
He say anything else?
没有
No.
就让我们所有人回去
Just to come back. All of us.
他怎么说的
How he say it?
你知道 直说呗
You know, he just said it.
- 靠 - 就是
- Fuck. - Yeah.
该死
Shit.
- 还是那样一口咬定? - 没错
- They holding to it? - So far.
好吧
All right.
没弄错时间?
They got the times right?
里程数呢
How about the mileage?
好吧
All right.
我再问你一次
So I'm gonna ask you one more time.
你没见他下过车?
You never saw him out the car?
没有
No.
你一直跟他待在一起?
You stayed with him the whole time?
一直
Every minute.
他出停车场用了多久
How long before he came out the parking garage?
他独处的时间多长
How long was he on his own?
没时间耍花样 String
Not enough time to do shit, String.
他进出大概花了三分钟
He was in and out, like, in three minutes.
冷静
Chill.
东西就这么没了
This shit is fucked up.
- 听着... - 你们完全照着指示?
- Look-- - You follow the directions?
- 就跟你说的一样 - 里程数记下了?
- I did just like you told me. - Wrote down the mileage?
- 嗯 - 我看看
- Yeah. - Let me see.
看吧 就这
See, right there.
不 你多开了十分之三英里 老兄
No, you're three-tenths of a mile long, dawg.
如果你们遵照指示就不会这样了
And if you followed directions, you wouldn't be.
String 该做的我都做了 伙计 我发誓
String, I did everything like I should, man. I swear.
想清楚了吗
You got answers?
要不是他们封锁了Boulevard几个街区...
You didn't have to take a detour in Camden...
你们就没必要在Camden绕路
when they shut down a couple of blocks on the Boulevard?
你伤了脚?
You hurt your foot?
我的脚?
My foot?
你知道 你那样踢千斤顶
You know, the way you kicked that tire jack.
- 你一直在监视我们? - 谁 我?
- You was on us the whole time? - Who, me?
你让人跟踪我们
Y'all had people following us.
那东西到底在哪
So where it at?
你知道 你该让我跟你一起去
You know, you should take me with you.
我该见见这些人 如果我见了这些人...
I should meet these guys. If I meet these guys...
我们就能做成生意 知道我在说什么吗
we can figure out ways to do business. You know what I'm saying?
Zig 那些家伙是来真的
Zig, these guys are real.
怎么 我就不是?
What, I ain't real?
...六度
Six degrees.
人人都赶回家吃泡菜庆圣诞...
Everybody's going home to sauerkraut and Santy Claus...
我们偏偏反其道而行...
and here comes a gang of us walking the other way...
Little Big Roy还拄着木腿
Little Big Roy with his wooden leg.
- 老天 还有木铲 - 就是
- Christ, them wooden shovels. - Yeah.
你们这些孩子对木铲一无所知吧
You children don't know nothing about them wooden shovels, do you?
弄粮食时可不能弄出火星来
Can't have no sparks when you working grain.
- 轰 - 更像是咔彭
- Kaboom. - It's more like kaput.
现在Bawlmer看不到运粮船了 朋友
You never gonna see another grain ship here in Bawlmer, my friends.
Zig 你相信这些个活化石吗
Zig, you believe these fucking dinosaurs?
他们成天坐在这说过去 怎么用木铲卸货...
They sit around all day talking shit about how they used to off-load with shovels...
怎么用背拖铁轨车
and carry fucking railroad cars on their backs.
还有用消防水管喝威士忌
Shit, and drink whiskey through a fire hose.
回家干老婆到早上  真是一群老廉颇
Go home and fuck their wives till breakfast. There was some heroes back then.
今晚的陈年烂谷子还真多啊
Shit is thick in here tonight, gentlemen.
你能怎样 这代人就是这么无知
What can you do? This generation, they just don't know.
- 不复当年咯 - 对 确实
- Ain't never gonna be what it was. - No, indeed.
每晚跟这些老东西一起 就像在1952年
Every night with these old fucks. It's like 1952 and shit.
小子们 要知道 我像你们这么大时
Boys, you know, when I was your age,
我一天卸十条船
I unloaded ten ships a goddamn day.
要知道 我用一只胳膊...
You know, I'd do it with one arm...
就能扛起一袋300磅的波兰假阳具
after a 300-pound bag of Polish dildos fell on me.
哇哦 等等 什么叫做波兰假阳具
Whoa, wait. What the fuck is a Polish dildo?
事实上 在我家 那也叫"波兰大熏肠"
Actually, at my house, it's a ring of kielbasa.
老天 又来了
Christ, here we go again.
来啊 秀秀你的漂亮宝贝
Bring out pretty boy.
不过你瞧 在你们的老家 我肯定随便一点"老式早餐"就满足了
But, you know, where you boys hail from, I'm sure any old breakfast link will do.
你们都知道他要把小弟弟掏出来 对吧
You know he's gonna pull out his dick, right?
这小子真有问题
That boy ain't right.
只有我...
It was just me...
我的老木腿和旧木铲...
and my old wooden leg, and my old wooden shovel...
还有我的玻璃眼和波兰小铅笔
and my glass eye, and my Polish pencil.
说得工会里的人没使过真家伙似的
Like anyone from the Checkers Local ever used anything but a real pencil.
靠 他们还没有了呢
Shit, they don't even push one of them no more.
就会说些陈年破事
Talking trash about 1514.
老天啊 知道吗 全员到右舷
Jesus H. Christ, you know what? All hands starboard.
快
Come on.
这破船在侧倾 感觉到了吗
The old tub is listing. Can you feel her?
知道为啥吗
You wanna know why?
因为这些老东西卸了太多货...
'Cause them old fucks done unloaded so much bullshit...
这破船就要翻了
that this whole motherfucker's gonna capsize.
稳住 我们在下沉
Brace yourselves, we're sinking.
该死 Ziggy
God damn it, Ziggy.
今天不许再把你那东西掏出来
You're not taking your dick out in here again.
我给你们这些老东西看点巨无霸
Let me show you old gents some bulk cargo
你们谁也搬不动
that none of you could ever handle.
谁说不复当年了?
Who says they don't make them like they used to?
帅小伙今晚进城了
Pretty boy is on the town tonight.
Ziggy这死小子
Fucking Ziggy, man.
把她弄上船?
Bring her in the boat?
该死 不
Hell, no.
如果把她弄上来 她会四分五裂的
She'll fall apart if we try to bring her in.
那怎么办
What's the plan then?
把她好好勾着
We'll hook her real good.
我们慢慢拖回码头
We'll tow her slowly over to the pier.
她看上去如何
What's she look like?
什么意思
What do you mean?
你觉得在水里泡了多久
How long you think she's been in?
没多久
She's fresh.
不过腿断了
Legs are broke, though.
也许是从桥上跳下来的
Probably a jumper from the bridge.
行了 妈 醒了
All right, Ma. Shit.
嘿 Zig...Ziggy
Yo Zig...Ziggy
厨房关门了
Kitchen's closed.
不能准时起床赶船的醉鬼没东西吃
There's no service for drunks who can't get up in time to catch a ship.
什么船
What ship?
你老爸说Talco Line号今天到
Your father says the Talco Line is in today.
北角就有两艘船了
That makes two ships at North Point.
是Atlantic Light号 下午才到
It's the Atlantic Light. Ain't due until this afternoon.
那也不是借口
That still is no excuse.
早上好 老妈
Good morning, Mom.
两个烂醉鬼
Couple of goddamn drunks I got.
走的时候别忘了带上你堂弟
And don't leave without taking your cousin with you.
我要大扫除 不想他在那躺尸
I gotta clean in there, and I ain't gonna do it around his carcass.
你在卖关子 不是吗 Stan?
You keep us guessing, don't you, Stan?
礼拜天的弥撒见不着人
At Sunday mass, you can't be found.
周二早上 倒是带来一批军队
But early on a Tuesday, you arrive with an army.
2500元 我和三个分局...
$2,500 from myself and every other Polack...
及四个消防局的其他波兰人给你的
in three districts and four firehouses.
- 如此馈赠我该何以为报 - 一个惊喜
- And to what do we owe such generosity? - A surprise.
你重修中殿 我们就订了个彩窗
We ordered up a window for where you renovated the nave.
算是个纪念 看看
A memorial. Let me see that.
致波兰裔警员与消防员
To Polish police and firefighters.
我们在Glen Burnie找来的能工巧匠
Found this craftsman down in Glen Burnie that you would not believe.
- 放中殿? - 对 放中殿
- For the nave? - Yeah, for the nave.
二楼的教区寓所也要一扇窗户
We could use another window on the second floor of the rectory.
- 教区寓所? - 楼上过道
- The rectory? - The upstairs hallway.
码头的人为这个窗出了多少钱
How much did them dock boys offer for this spot?
我照付
I can match it.
捐赠是保密的 Stan
Offerings are confidential, Stan.
你也看见了...
And as you can see--
我能出4000块
I can go as high as $4,000.
如果比4000还多你就出个声
Just tell me if they went higher than $4,000.
超过4000? 就那些码头工?
More than $4,000? From the docks?
该死的....
How the hell....
抱歉 神父
I'm sorry, Father.
谁来捐的
Who came to you with the offer?
Francis Sobotka
Francis Sobotka.
Frank Sobotka有这么多钱?
Frank Sobotka has that kind of money?
- 是他的工会出的 - 工会?
- It was from his local. - The Checkers?
他们连100个付费会员都找不出
They don't have 100 guys left paying dues.
那个教区的人无私奉献 Stan
It's a parish of givers, Stan.
也许你可以跟Frank谈谈
Maybe you talk to Frank.
找出个解决办法
Work it out somehow.
嗯 会谈的
Yeah, we'll talk.
警长?
Major?
豪华港口房和出租公寓 低至300美元
哇哦 这不是"水手Barnacle Bill"(一首歌)吗
Well, if it isn't Barnacle Bill, the sailor.
Ray 最近可好
Ray, how you been?
今年除了积案我一无所获
I got nothing but red ink under my name this year.
Landsman现在就是个乱咬人的混球
Landsman's become an asshole with teeth.
钓到大鱼了?
Fish your wish, huh?
跳河 大概吧
Jumper, probably.
离桥很近
This close to the bridge.
大概是吧 挺漂亮的
Probably, yeah. Pretty, though.
是啊
She is, yeah.
我今早进男厕时
I go into the men's room this morning.
猜猜谁在我旁边隔间吐得天昏地暗
Guess who's in the next stall puking his guts out.
- Bunk Moreland - 你怎么知道的
- Bunk Moreland. - How'd you know?
那废物喝酒毫无节制
Useless fuck can't hold his liquor.
- 外面怎么样 伙计? - 最近可好 Fam?
- What's happening, man? - What's up, Fam?
都好
All right.
还没有Roberto那边的消息?
You ain't heard from Roberto yet?
屁都没一个 伙计
Not a goddamn word, man.
Billy还拿着我们的钱 对吧
Billy still got our money though, right?
所以你得去趟纽约 伙计
So you need to get down to New York, man.
这家伙玩什么花样
Fuck kind of game this nigger playing?
你相信我们的人?
You sure of our people?
我彻查了他们的话 都没问题
I broke down all their stories and they came back clean.
另外 我还找了可靠的人看着他们
Besides, I had some good people watching them.
是吗?
Oh,yeah?
- 谁? - Tank和Country
- Who? - Tank, Country.
那混球回家多久了
How long that motherfucker been home?
才一个月 还在假释期 他说"去他的"
A month. Still on parole. He said, "fuck that."
- 直接回了组织 - 不错
- Straight back in the mix. - All right.
那很好 错不在我 是Roberto的问题
So good, it ain't on us. It's on Roberto.
把事办妥 懂我的意思吗
Set it straight. You know what I mean?
硬的不行来软的 但要有原则
So when you go hard on them, take it light, but be firm.
他们钱到手了 我们却没拿到货
They got our money and we ain't got the product.
明白吗 这可不行
So, you feel me? The shit ain't right.
你在里面过得怎样 B?
How you fixed in here otherwise, B?
没什么 伙计 懂我的意思吗
This ain't no thing, man. You know what I mean?
既来之 则安之
You come in here, man, you get your mind right.
在这只有两天
You get in here and you do two days.
进这烂地的那天...
It's the day you come in this motherfucker--
- 和离开这烂地的那天 - 没错
- And the day you get out this motherfucker. - That's right.
就这么回事
Exactly.
- 什么事 - 最近如何
- What's up? - How you doing?
- 从职业介绍所过来? - 今天晚些时候要卸Atlantic上的货
- Coming from the hiring hall? - I'm working the Atlantic late today.
- 47分会现在怎样 - 一团糟
- How's it looking for Local 47? - You're shit out of luck.
没点资历的 根本排不上班
ROIROs isn't going to anybody lower than a G-series.
运气好 顶多能去卸半天货...
Best you can get, maybe half a day doing break-bulk...
还是在Locust角卸卸铝
on an aluminum load at Locust Point.
才半天 嗯?
Half a day, huh?
真它妈的倚老卖老
Seniority sucks.
- 是啊 如果你资格不够的话 - 嗯 说得没错
- Yeah, if you ain't senior, it does. - Yeah, you got that right.
- 我走了 - 嗯 回见
- I'm out of here. - Yeah, I'll see you.
你它妈干嘛不叫醒我
The fuck you ain't wake me up for?
现在才起 蠢货?
Just getting up now, fuck-face?
不 事实上 你妈做了顿丰盛的早餐
No, actually, your ma makes a good breakfast.
- 不可能 - 培根鸡蛋 宝贝
- No fucking way. - Bacon and eggs, baby.
你要去见"希腊人" 对吧
You going down to see the Greek, right?
拜托 伙计 我不会搞砸的
Come on, man. I ain't gonna fuck it up for you.
看在上帝的份上 你上车就是 行吗
For Christ's sake, will you just get in the car already?
快 出发了
Come on. Let's go.
我对天发誓 Ziggy 你开口我就要你小命
I swear to God, Ziggy. You open your mouth, I'll fucking kill you.
- 码头来的Nicky - Spiros
- Nicky, from the docks. - Spiros.
- 最近可好 - 好
- How are you? Good? - good.
- 他是谁 - 这是Zig 我叔叔的儿子
- Who's your friend? - This is Zig, my uncle's kid.
- 你叔叔? Frankie? - 对
- Your uncle? Frankie? - Yeah.
Ziggy是他大儿子
Ziggy's his oldest.
我车坏了 他送我来的
My car broke down, you know. He drove.
你就是"希腊人"
So you must be the Greek.
嗯 反正我是希腊人
Well, I'm Greek anyway.
Boris Badanoff
Boris Badanoff.
常在附件见到你 对吧
I know you from around the way, right?
为啥叫我Boris 我想不明白
Why am I Boris? I don't understand this.
到哪都叫我Boris
Everywhere I am Boris.
靠 你是俄罗斯人 不是吗
Shit, you're Russian, right?
不 乌克兰人 Kyiv是乌克兰的
No, Ukraine. Kyiv is Ukraine.
- 应该差不到哪去 - 错 差远了
- It's the same difference, though. - No, you're wrong.
有什么关系 你不喜欢别人叫你Boris?
What's the matter? You don't like being called Boris?
叫Sergei
Sergei.
不是吧 伙计 Boris好听多了
No way, man. Boris is way better.
就像卡通人物
It's like the guy from the cartoon.
Boris和Natasha?(美国60年代动画人物)
Boris and Natasha?
Bullwinkle 伙计 Rocky和Bullwinkle
Bullwinkle, man. Rocky and Bullwinkle.
要咖啡吗 小鬼?
You want some coffee, pie?
不用了
No, I'm good.
- 你们有什么馅饼 - 嘿 Zig
- Actually, what kind of pie you got? - Hey, Zig.
他妈的闭嘴 懂吗
Shut the fuck up, huh?
傻B
Malaka.
不 不 他挺好的
No, it's cool. He's cool.
- Frank的小鬼? - 对
- That's Frank's kid? - Yeah.
他也是工会的人 你知道
He's in the Union, you know.
但是他还很菜 排不上什么班
But he's like an L-series, so he ain't getting any hours.
老交易 老价钱
Same deal, same rate.
行 谁开车
All right. Who's driving?
又是他?
Again?
要做得更隐蔽点
You want to mix it up a little more.
就别让海关认得熟面孔
Make it so customs doesn't put no names to faces.
疑人不用 用人不疑
You trust a man, you stay with him.
- 行 - 好的
- Okay. - All right.
- 就Boris了 - Sergei
- Boris it is. - Sergei.
随便啦
Yeah, whatever.
过来 傻帽 走了
Come on, fucknuts. Let's go.
- 那个开面火鸡三明治怎样 - 不咋地 走了
- How's the open-face turkey? - It's shit. Let's go.
各位回见
See you guys later.
Bullwinkle?
波兰佬
Polacks.
你他妈让我很丢脸 伙计
You fucking embarrassed me in there, man.
你自找的 Zig
You embarrassed yourself, Zig.
看见我侄子了吗
You seen my nephew anywhere?
Nick? 没见到
Nick? Not yet.
他今天不用上班吧
I don't think he got any hours.
- 嘿 Frank - 嘿 亲爱的
- Hey, Frank. - Hey, darling.
为了让我能早点弄好报告
Just so I can finish my paperwork early,
能告诉我你们今天要偷什么吗
what are your people gonna steal today?
不知道
I don't know.
几辆豪华轿车 宽屏彩电
Couple luxury sedans, some color TVs, wide-screen.
也许还有几瓶伏特加 也许是一整船集装箱
Maybe a couple cans of vodka, maybe a whole container ship.
好吧 马到成功
Okay. Y'all have a good one.
你让她这样把你耍着玩?
You let her fuck with you like that?
她人不坏
She's all right.
我喜欢她
I like her.
查过电脑了 9区11号单元
I checked the computer. It's Bay 9, Cell 11.
最底下
It's right on the bottom.
你在忙Light号上的货 对吧
You working the light, ain't you?
我去办 对
I'm on it, yeah.
他们还说了什么
Did they say anything else?
没什么 就说价格跟以前一样
No. Just that it's the same money to us.
走吧
Let's go.
行了 Frank叔叔
All right, Uncle Frank.
- Winona - Jimmy 最近哪去了
- Winona. - Jimmy, where you been?
Jay
看看谁来了 水手
Look who it is. Sailor Boy.
- 你欠我10美元 - 去你的
- You owe me $10. - Fuck you.
你告诉了Rawls我不想去哪 都是你害的 Jay
You told Rawls where I didn't wanna go. You made it happen, Jay.
我不过是告诉他你不想去哪
I told him where you didn't wanna go.
对 接着他们就把我派那去了
Yeah, and they sent me there.
我知道Rawls怒了 但不知道有多火大
I knew Rawls was pissed, I didn't know how pissed.
我能说什么呢
What can I tell you?
Bunk哪去了
Where's Bunk?
和Crutchfield出勤去了
Out on a call with Crutchfield.
那女孩是怎么回事 从桥上跳下来还是怎么的
What's up with the girl? She come off the bridge or what?
Frazier医生今天做了尸检
Doc Frazier posted her today.
头部和胸部有钝器伤
Blunt-force trauma to the head and chest.
他说触水前她已经死了
He says she's dead before she hits the water.
那抵抗伤呢
What about the defense wounds?
三只手指上有瘀伤?
Bruising on three fingers?
把她捞上来时就看到了
We saw that as soon as we picked her up.
你们都没注意到?
You missed the defense wounds?
我没看 我以为她是自杀的
I wasn't looking. Thought she went off the bridge.
还有 她在水里没穿外套和鞋子
Also, she's in the drink with no coat or shoes.
也许掉水里了 也许没有
Maybe that stuff comes off in the water, maybe not.
但我不认为大冬天的她会穿那样上桥
I don't see her going to the bridge in winter dressed like she was.
个人观点
But then that's just me.
跟Bunk说我来过 行吗
Tell Bunk I was here, will you?
工作愉快
Have fun.
已经很愉快了
We already had our fun.
把她扔给Baltimore郡了(此地为独立市 不归郡管辖)
Dumping her on Baltimore County.
丢给郡了?
On the County?
你们在桥东发现她
You fished her out east of the bridge.
那是Baltimore郡 她归他们管
That's Baltimore County. She's their stat.
你就这么说服他们的?
You sold them on that?
Rawls说的
Rawls did.
他打给那的警监 说
He called up the Colonel and said:
"你手头又多了件无头案"
"You got one hell of a murder on your hands."
这就是自我保护 Jimmy
It's all about self-preservation, Jimmy.
你这辈子也学不会
Something you never learned.
嘿 Norris 州警 2线
Hey, Norris. State Police, Line 2.
往右边一点
A little to the right!
好 放吧
Good, bring her down!
东西在那了 随时可以来取
It's there whenever they want it.
你是我委托人 Bell先生...
Now that you are my client, Mr. Bell...
我们享有律师与客户的信息披露豁免权
we are protected by the attorney-client privilege.
我还以为Roberto会过来
I thought Roberto would be here.
不大可能
Not likely.
恐怕这事已经上了周一的报纸
This, I'm afraid, was in Monday's papers.
Roberto Castellano Silva 看样子被药管局盯上了
It seems Roberto Castellano y Silva has been targeted by the DEA.
因此我们生意做不成了?
That's why we didn't do the business?
现在 Roberto和他手下
Right now, Roberto and his people
不想卷入任何...
aren't going to be getting involved in anything...
会让情况变得更复杂的事
that could further complicate the situation.
你知道 通常找个人担了罪后 你就可以重新做生意了...
You know, usually, when you take a fall, you get right back in there...
因为到时就没人盯着了 不是吗
'cause you know nobody's watching, right?
有时是
Sometimes.
有时你会担心自己究竟是怎么暴露的
And sometimes you wonder how it is you got caught in the first place.
于是选择改变模式
And you decide to change the pattern.
他拿了我们的钱?
He took our money?
你钱一到我们麻烦就来了
Your advance payment arrived as our problem did.
他们说钱正返回Baltimore
And I'm told the money is on the way back to Baltimore.
知道吗 我觉得你在指责我们...
You know, I get the feeling that you're blaming us...
害Roberto陷入困境
for Roberto's predicament.
可能你们在Baltimore的问题 与我委托人在这的问题...
Perhaps your problems in Baltimore and my client's problems here...
只是巧合
are coincidental.
- 但现阶段... - 听我说
- But right now-- - Listen to me.
我们遭受打击他是第一个知道的
He was the first to know that we took a hit.
他知道现在没人能动我们...
He knows no one came close to rolling over us...
那案子的所有文件他都知道
and all the documents from the case.
尽管如此 还是有些问题要考虑
Nonetheless, we have a legitimate concern.
考虑到Barksdale经营的业务...
Considering the scope of Mr. Barksdale's operation...
他的判决 最起码可说很轻
his sentence was, to say the least, mild.
但如果有可能 虽然可能性很低...
But if the possibility exists, however unlikely...
如果他被轻判是因为跟警方合作...
that the leniency he received was the result of cooperation....
怎么
what?
我相信你明白我们的处境
You understand our position, I'm sure.
Frank 那东西就放在那...
Frank, it's sitting out there waiting...
而那混账俄国佬还不把它运出码头
and this Russian fuck won't take it off the pier.
我没瞎
I ain't blind.
我不喜欢那东西在外面放那么长时间
I don't like it sitting out in the open that long.
海关封条已经破了 会被人发现的
The customs seal is broke. Somebody's gonna see it.
我们会被人抓到小辫子的
Our asses are hanging out here.
- 喂 - Nicky 怎么回事 东西还没弄走
- Yeah? - Nicky, what the fuck? It's still here.
- 靠 - 就是
- Shit. - Yeah.
- Sergei哪去了 - 他停在外面
- Where's Sergei? - He's parked at the end of the lot.
- 他在等什么 - 我它妈的怎么知道
- What's he waiting for? - I got no fucking idea.
但船快清空了 他们得早点弄走
But the ship's almost empty. They need to shit or get off the pot.
- 我去问问 - 嗯
- I'll look into it. - Yeah.
好的 明白
Okay, I understand.
靠 找个车把它弄走藏在货堆里 我们处境不妙
Fuck it. Get it on a fifth wheel and lose it in the stack. We're at risk.
我不想撒谎 这些文书工作真烦人
I ain't lying when I say this paperwork is kicking my ass.
也许吧 但至少结束一天工作
Maybe so. But the end of the day,
你能完整地回来
you come through the door in one piece.
你就爱这么想
You like to think so.
但被纸划伤的地方开始痛了
But all these paper cuts are starting to take their toll.
你这性感大侦探
You big, nasty detective.
过来
Come here.
让我亲亲你的小伤口
Let me give your little boo-boo a kiss.
这么多?
All this?
刚开始
I'm just getting started.
1000美元给医生
$1000 for the doctor.
每次1000美元 女友
$1000 each time, girlfriend.
直到我怀孕为止
Every month till I'm pregnant.
总有更好的办法
There's gotta be a better way.
那就靠你了 甜心
That would be on you, sweetheart.
要是找到合适的捐精者 我们就不用付那么多了
Come up with a suitable donor and we pay a lot less.
除非用你的B 否则我才不想跟那些男人做
Not with your pussy would I fuck anyone of these guys.
你刚刚说什么 不 你不能那样说
What did you just say? No, you didn't just say that.
Willam A.Rawls警监 刑侦科(Rawls从警长升为警监)
警司
Sergeant.
你的浮尸又回来了
Your floater's come back.
郡警又把她归到桥这边了
County boys are putting her on our side of the bridge.
- 不可能 - 嗯
- No fucking way. - Yeah.
我们水警队中某个废柴...
Some useless fuck in our Marine Unit faxed them a report...
大清早给他们传真了一份潮水和风向报告
on the early morning tides and wind currents.
表明尸体是在桥西落水 飘到了桥东
Shows the body went in the water west of the bridge and drifted out.
McNulty
McNulty.
混账Jimmy 整我们来寻开心
Fucking Jimmy. Fucking with us for the fun of it.
为这事我得给那狗娘养的些嘉奖
I gotta give the son of a bitch some credit for wit on this one.
C~T~G~D
Cocksucker.
M~L~G~B
Motherfucker.
钱数没错 还有什么货
The count is right. What's on the shelf?
Mace正带10份过来 所以Moe Man手头大约38份
Mace carrying 10 down here. So, Moe Man holding about 38 up top.
我查了储备 没多少了
I checked the stash, and we way low.
- Moe Man动了我们的东西 - 他手头有多少
- Moe Man taking our shit. - What he holding?
他说有30来份 但我知道肯定没有
He say he holds about 30-something, but I know that ain't right.
我要教训教训他
I'm gonna fuck him up.
你就知道找人干架
First thing you think to do is fuck a nigger up.
你那木头脑袋何时才能明白...
When your brick brain gonna realize there's more to this...
我们要做的不只揍人那么简单?
than just thumpin' on niggers?
- Moe应该有多少 - 38份 大概
- What Moe supposed to be holding? - 38, thereabout.
- 你他妈白痴啊? - 那很快就没了
- Ain't you the damn fool? - But then we low.
听着 小子 如果没货了 那是String的意思
Look, nigger, if we low, it 'cause String want us that way.
他让我们有货我们就有了
When he wants us up, we be up.
String说了算
String is on top of the shit.
都得听他的
He on top of everything.
回你们的位置去 伙计
Go back to your spot, man.
混账McNulty
Fucking McNulty.
黑色表示已破案件，红色表示未破
"潮汐王子"(一部电影)
The Prince of Tides.
J.DOE 无名氏。一般用Jane Doe表示女性，John Doe表示男性。
- 兄弟 你觉得今天够彪悍吗 - 嗯
- Brother, you feeling strong today? - Yeah.
看你能不能把他从椅子上弄起来
See if you can get his ass out of that chair.
他说你要扁他也没关系
He said it was fine if you wanted to hit him, too.
47分会的家伙做完爱后,第一件要做的事是什么?
What's the first thing a guy from Local 47 does after he gets laid?
- 是什么 - 擦掉眼里的防狼喷雾
- What? - Wipes the pepper spray from his eyes.
嘿 Frank 有情况
Hey, Frank. Something's going on.
是女孩子 伙计 很年轻
It's fucking girls, man. Young ones.
有十几个呢
There's a dozen of them.
死了? 她们死了?
Dead? They're dead?